edtechreview.in 2015-02-16

# Privacy Policy

                                    Privacy Policy
The EdTechReview India website is made available by EdTechReview (ETR), an
initiative by Eduvative Technologies LLP. EdTechReview India respects your privacy
and recognizes your need for appropriate protection and management of your personal
information, such as your name and email address.
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, and know how your personal information is
collected and used by us. Contact us with any questions you may have by emailing
privacy@edtechreview.co. We are always happy to hear from you.
WHO CAN USE?
Anyone can view our Web site, but a free account and/or subscription is required for
access to the full range of information and online services.
WHAT INFORMATION DOES EDTECHREVIEW INDIA COLLECT AND
HOW?
Personal information collected by EdTechReview India is information voluntarily
provided to us by you when you subscribe to our newsletter or contact us with a query or
by creating an account on the site. Currently, information that we save about you
includes your email address and, optionally, your first and last name and any other
information voluntarily provided. This information is maintained on secure third-party
servers. You may unsubscribe from our email distribution lists via a link at the bottom
of every newsletter, which removes your information from our mailing system system
and the third-party systems we utilize. Even after unsubscribing, we will keep your
details for records but would not use them for the usual operations.
In case of premium reports and case studies, even if offered by us as “free”, we may also
ask for your physical mailing address, organization, name, email and phone number.
You will be notified of possible disclosure to third party sponsors at the time you request
a report, prior to confirming your order. Sponsors may use your mailing address to
contact you regarding offers that they feel may be of interest to you. We have no control
over the use a Sponsor may make of your contact information.
If you chose to make a comment on our site, your user name or profile picture or both
may appear alongside your comment. Comments are stored on our secure third-party
server. Additionally, the EdTechReview India website uses "cookies" to track and collect
information about you and your visit to our site, such as IP address, browser, operating

system, time of visit, etc. A cookie is a small string of text that a website can send to your
browser, for the purpose of enhancing our understanding of site user activity and your
visit to the website. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass
on computer viruses, or capture your email address. You can set your computer settings
to alert you when a cookie is being placed. You may also clear all cookies saved to your
computer by using the relevant selection in your internet browser. We use cookie
information to understand from where in the world our site traffic comes. Based upon
the information collected by cookies, we may also suggest posts or show ads that we
think will be of interest to you.
We also use caching and a cached data may be stored on the user machine depending on
the web browser setting. Through caching we try to improve the content delivery speed
for better user experience. You may clear the cached data by options provided in your
web browser.
Our site uses third-party tools (eg. Google analytics, Facebook connect, Google+ and
others) that may also use cookies to collect anonymous data. Advertisers on our site may
also place cookies. We have no control over how third-party tools and advertisers use
cookies.
HOW EDTECHREVIEW INDIA USES YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
When you choose to provide us your email address, we may use it to send you our
newsletter (if you have so requested) or to reply to a message that you have sent to us.
EdTechReview India does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. We
will not disclose your personal information to others without your express permission,
other than as set forth in this privacy policy. EdTechReview India does not supplement
the personal information provided by you with information collected from other
sources.
We may perform statistical, demographic, and marketing analyses of account holders
and their subscribing and purchasing patterns, for product-development purposes and
to inform advertisers about the nature of our Web traffic. We also use such information
to allow advertising to be targeted, in aggregate, to readers for whom such advertising is
most pertinent.
We may also use your personal information to contact you from time to time by email
regarding updates to our policies or to send you other information that we feel may be of
interest to you. We may email you about events to be held or attended by EdTechReview
India or other partner events and offers that we feel may be of interest to you.

EdTechReview India may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets,
including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition,
reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.
We may also release personal information when we believe release is appropriate to
comply with the law or to protect the rights of EdTechReview India or others. Your
personal information is, of course, subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other
government subpoenas, warrants or orders.
HOW DOES EDTECHREVIEW INDIA PROTECT                               YOUR PERSONAL
INFORMATION?
When you provide us with your email or other personal information, these are stored in
a secure third-party database in encrypted format.
REVIEWING,          CHANGING            AND      DELETING       YOUR      PERSONAL
INFORMATION
At any time, you may request to view or update the personal information that is
associated with your account and stored by EdTechReview India. You may also request
that we correct, delete some or all personal and/or non-personal information that we
have collected about you. We will promptly fulfill your request and provide you
confirmation when the information has been deleted. To request any change or deletion
of your personal information, or your entire EdTechReview India account, send a
request to privacy@edtechreview.co.
THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES
The EdTechReview India website may include links to third-party websites. We do not
have control over third-party websites and applications, or their information collection
practices. The practices of third-party websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.
We recommend that you consult the privacy policies of the third-party websites and
applications or contact their providers directly for information about their privacy
practices. EdTechReview India assumes no liability for the practices of third-party
websites and applications.
PAID PRODUCT AND SERVICES
While much of our Web site and online services is free, we do charge fees for certain
premium content, products, and services. To enable the purchase of these products, we
collect and store billing and encrypted credit-card information. This information will
only be shared with third parties who perform tasks required to complete the purchase
transaction.

READER SURVEYS AND MARKET RESEARCH
EdTechReview India may collect personal information from readers in connection with
voluntary surveys. Data may be collected on our Web site, on a survey company's Web
site, on the phone, or through the mail. The information you provide in answer to survey
questions may be shared, but only in the aggregate, with advertisers and partners unless
we notify you otherwise at the time of collection. You have the right to decline to
participate in any survey.
CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY
Because the Internet is constantly evolving, so are our policies. By accessing the
EdTechReview India website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as it may be
amended from time to time. Any updates to this Privacy Policy will be posted here. It is
your responsibility and you agree to check back to view the policy at this site from time
to time. We may also notify you of material changes by sending you an email.
DO YOU HAVE QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS?
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or our information practices, or
any concerns about the security of your personal information, please contact
EdTechReview India at privacy@edtechreview.co. We will revert to you as soon as
possible.
By using India.Edtechreview.co, you are agreeing to the terms of our User Agreement.
